<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="pretty-atom-feed.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>Blog Title</title>
  <subtitle>This is a longer description about your blog.</subtitle>
  <link href="https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/feed/feed.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/" />
  <updated>2024-08-24T21:06:40Z</updated>
  <id>https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Your Name</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Internet Is Culture: Why Web3 Is the Future of Human Connection</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/blog/Internet%20is%20Culture/" />
    <updated>2024-08-24T21:06:40Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/blog/Internet%20is%20Culture/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;internet-is-culture-why-web3-is-the-future-of-human-connection&quot;&gt;Internet Is Culture: Why Web3 Is the Future of Human Connection&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We must acknowledge a simple but profound truth:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The internet is no longer just a platform—it is culture itself.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every aspect of our lives is now mediated through the digital realm, and the way we navigate this space will define the future of human connection. Web3 is not just an investment opportunity; it is the foundation upon which the next era of culture will be built.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The rest of this is transcribed from the video essay by &#39;ArtChad&#39; on YouTube. All rights respective of their authors.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-internets-political-shift-the-death-of-the-normie-creator&quot;&gt;The Internet&#39;s Political Shift: The Death of the &amp;quot;Normie&amp;quot; Creator&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cultural landscape of the internet has undergone a seismic shift. What was once a space for entertainment and mild discourse has transformed into a battleground of political ideologies and authenticity tests. The internet has become an all-encompassing hyperobject, where everything is connected, and nothing can be avoided—including politics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;from-taboo-to-ubiquitous-the-politicization-of-everything&quot;&gt;From Taboo to Ubiquitous: The Politicization of Everything&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was a time when politics was a topic to be avoided, especially in casual settings like the dinner table. It was something your grandfather might bring up, making everyone uncomfortable until the subject was quickly changed to maintain peace. Politics, back then, had a clear definition: it was about government, policy, and the actions of those in power. Today, however, that definition has expanded to include virtually everything—from the culture of financial institutions to the personal grooming habits of public figures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this new era, even the most mundane aspects of life are viewed through a political lens. Whether it&#39;s the appearance of a politician or the political affiliations of celebrities, everything is scrutinized. The internet, as the dominant medium of communication, fuels this trend by thriving on engagement, often driven by the most controversial and divisive content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-internets-new-reality-no-room-for-the-normie&quot;&gt;The Internet&#39;s New Reality: No Room for the &amp;quot;Normie&amp;quot;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this hyper-politicized environment, no creator can remain neutral or apolitical. Even the most seemingly harmless internet figures, like Mr. Beast or Charlie (Moist Critical), find themselves embroiled in controversies that go beyond simple online drama. Mr. Beast&#39;s current controversy isn&#39;t just about a creepy friend; it&#39;s tied to deeper societal issues, like the role of transgender people in media. Similarly, Charlie&#39;s debate with Sneeko isn&#39;t just about their differing opinions—it’s about how he got roped into a political discussion that his audience wasn&#39;t used to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reality is that the internet now demands creators to take clear stances on political issues, whether they want to or not. The days of building a massive following by being a &amp;quot;nice guy&amp;quot; who avoids controversy are over. Audiences are no longer content with surface-level engagement; they demand transparency and authenticity. They want to know where creators stand on the issues that matter to them, and they won&#39;t accept anything less.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-collapse-of-the-nice-guy-empire&quot;&gt;The Collapse of the Nice Guy Empire&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &amp;quot;nice guy&amp;quot; persona, once a safe and effective way to build an online presence, is no longer viable. Creators who try to maintain a neutral or uncontroversial stance are finding that their audiences either force them to reveal their true beliefs or turn on them when those beliefs are finally exposed. We see this in the rise of politically engaged creators like Aiden Ross, iShowSpeed, and the Nelk Boys, who have all taken clear stances on various issues, from supporting Trump to being pro-Palestine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even creators who were once considered &amp;quot;safe&amp;quot; are now choosing to get political. For instance, Pokimane, who has long been a non-controversial figure, is now openly pro-Palestine. This shift is not just about personal beliefs; it&#39;s about survival in a new internet landscape where being apolitical is no longer an option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-new-rules-of-the-internet&quot;&gt;The New Rules of the Internet&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re building a career on the internet today, you have to play by its new rules. You have to be transparent, authentic, and yes, political. The internet is now a radical, all-encompassing, and transparent medium. If you suppress your true self to maintain a broad audience, you risk building a following that doesn&#39;t really know you—and when they finally do, the backlash can be severe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Creators now face a difficult choice: be authentic and risk alienating parts of their audience, or try to remain neutral and risk losing credibility and relevance. The internet no longer allows for the nice guy or the normie. It&#39;s a new world, one where cultural shifts are rapid and unrelenting, and where audiences expect more than just entertainment—they expect creators to take a stand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion-the-end-of-the-normie-era&quot;&gt;Conclusion: The End of the Normie Era&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are witnessing the collapse of the nice guy empire and the death of the normie creator. The internet has changed, and with it, the expectations of those who consume content online. In this new world, you either pick a side, or your audience will force you to. The days of remaining apolitical or uncontroversial are over. The internet is no longer just a platform—it&#39;s the entirety of culture itself. And in this culture, authenticity and political engagement are no longer optional; they are essential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we move forward, creators will have to navigate this complex and often volatile landscape carefully. Those who fail to adapt will find themselves left behind, while those who embrace the new rules of the internet may thrive in ways they never imagined. It&#39;s a challenging time, but also an exciting one, where the power dynamics of online fame are being rewritten in real-time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, as you watch your favorite creators and engage with content online, remember: the audience isn&#39;t dumb, and they are paying attention to everything.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Preemptive Subrogation</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/blog/Preemptive%20Subrogation/" />
    <updated>2024-07-27T14:03:18Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/eleventy-base-blog/blog/Preemptive%20Subrogation/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-1-indemnification-agreement&quot;&gt;3.1 Indemnification Agreement&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;language-mermaid&quot; tabindex=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-mermaid&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;sequenceDiagram&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;participant&lt;/span&gt; Indemnifier
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;participant&lt;/span&gt; Indemnified
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;participant&lt;/span&gt; ThirdParty
    Indemnifier&lt;span class=&quot;token arrow operator&quot;&gt;-&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Indemnified&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Propose Indemnification Agreement
    Indemnified&lt;span class=&quot;token arrow operator&quot;&gt;-&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Indemnifier&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Review and Accept Agreement
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;Note over&lt;/span&gt; Indemnifier,Indemnified&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Agreement includes Scope, Limits, Duties, and Subrogation rights.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-2-claims-process&quot;&gt;3.2 Claims Process&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;language-mermaid&quot; tabindex=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-mermaid&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;sequenceDiagram&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;participant&lt;/span&gt; Indemnifier
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;participant&lt;/span&gt; Indemnified
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;participant&lt;/span&gt; ThirdParty
    Indemnified&lt;span class=&quot;token arrow operator&quot;&gt;-&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Indemnifier&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Notify of Loss
    Indemnifier&lt;span class=&quot;token arrow operator&quot;&gt;-&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Indemnified&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Investigate Claim
    Indemnifier&lt;span class=&quot;token arrow operator&quot;&gt;-&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Indemnified&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Approve and Pay Claim
    Indemnifier&lt;span class=&quot;token arrow operator&quot;&gt;-&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;ThirdParty&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Pursue Subrogation for Recovery&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-1-establishment-of-indemnification-pool&quot;&gt;5.1 Establishment of Indemnification Pool&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;language-mermaid&quot; tabindex=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-mermaid&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;sequenceDiagram&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;participant&lt;/span&gt; ProtocolDevelopers
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;participant&lt;/span&gt; Users
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;participant&lt;/span&gt; ExternalInvestors
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;participant&lt;/span&gt; IndemnificationPool
    ProtocolDevelopers&lt;span class=&quot;token arrow operator&quot;&gt;-&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;IndemnificationPool&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Contribute Funds
    Users&lt;span class=&quot;token arrow operator&quot;&gt;-&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;IndemnificationPool&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Contribute Funds
    ExternalInvestors&lt;span class=&quot;token arrow operator&quot;&gt;-&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;IndemnificationPool&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Contribute Funds
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;Note over&lt;/span&gt; ProtocolDevelopers,IndemnificationPool&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Pool dedicated to indemnification claims&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;risk-assessment-and-pricing&quot;&gt;Risk Assessment and Pricing&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;language-mermaid&quot; tabindex=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-mermaid&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;sequenceDiagram&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;participant&lt;/span&gt; RiskAssessors
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;participant&lt;/span&gt; Protocols
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;participant&lt;/span&gt; IndemnificationPool
    RiskAssessors&lt;span class=&quot;token arrow operator&quot;&gt;-&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Protocols&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Conduct Risk Assessment
    RiskAssessors&lt;span class=&quot;token arrow operator&quot;&gt;-&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;IndemnificationPool&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Determine Pricing Based on Risk
    IndemnificationPool&lt;span class=&quot;token arrow operator&quot;&gt;-&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Protocols&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Provide Indemnification Coverage
    &lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;Note over&lt;/span&gt; RiskAssessors,IndemnificationPool&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; Pricing based on protocol security,&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;language-mermaid!&quot; tabindex=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-mermaid!&quot;&gt;graph TD
    A[Data Collection] --&gt; B[AI Monitoring System]
    A --&gt; C[Community Feedback]
    B --&gt; D[Anomaly Detection]
    B --&gt; E[Predictive Analytics]
    B --&gt; F[NLP Analysis]
    C --&gt; G[User Surveys]
    C --&gt; H[Public Forum]
    C --&gt; I[Bounty Program]
    D --&gt; J[Improvement Proposals]
    E --&gt; J
    F --&gt; J
    G --&gt; J
    H --&gt; J
    I --&gt; J
    J --&gt; K[AI Ranking of Proposals]
    K --&gt; L[Community Discussion]
    L --&gt; M[DAO Voting]
    M --&gt;|Approved| N[Phased Rollout]
    N --&gt; O[Testnet Deployment]
    O --&gt; P[Gradual Mainnet Implementation]
    P --&gt; Q[Post-Implementation Monitoring]
    Q --&gt; R[System Audits]
    R --&gt; S[Audit Report Publication]
    S --&gt; A&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>